Se-no!
Garugaru-chan, go-go!
Please don't say it.
Because it's close.
It's close, it's close, you say?
Yes, please.
Let's say it out loud.
Yes!
Here we go.
Let's go! Let's go!
So, what's today?
Today is the 8th King.
This is the last one.
The last one.
We've come full circle.
Yes, we did.
So, for the last time, are you happy with the three of us?
Yes, we are.
Are you confident?
How are you feeling?
I'm not.
Stop it! And now you're going to say it out loud.
Well, no.
Not even a glance.
It's surprisingly difficult to be a king, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I've got some hard questions.
Of course, it's common.
No, but the question, the content of the question is also the content.
It's difficult.
Do you have a score when you become king?
Oh, well, he said you can go on a date with me.
You can go on a date with me.
I'll do my best.
You want me to do my best.
I'll try my best.
Shall we go?
Yes, I'm going.
Well then, let's start the video!
This time, I'm wearing T-HORIX's costume.
First question. What was your nickname as a child?
I don't know.
How much can I mention?
I think Minami might know.
So, like in elementary school?
Yeah, I guess so.
But I don't think I've never told her.
My friend asked me about this. She told me.
Yeah.
Let me guess.
I don't know. I don't remember.
What's your nickname now, by the way?
Yoka.
Sometimes Yokarin.
Oh, yeah, right.
It becomes.
I wonder.
I'm waiting for you.
No, no, no.
I didn't write two people.
What did you write?
You're early!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's not like that.
I'm done. Please do.
Se-no!
Yo.
You must be surprised. This.
Surprise!
It's easy to say.
Now, please answer the question.
What was your nickname as a child?
Let's see...
Y...yochi.
It's true.It's true.
Yotsuya! That way!
Nice try, but...
You're all so close.
It doesn't look like Yochi.
It's not Yotchi.
It doesn't look like Yotsuki.
Not Yotsuki, Yotchi?
I thought it was Yotchi.
Yes, that's everyone's point.
Please give us a minute.
Now, let's have Yui's problem.
What are you addicted to now?
Ah, this is easy.
Oh, I get it.
I think it would be better if you don't think of it as easy.
Eh!
The answer is, but it's common.
Did I just answer about me?
There are some, some.
Yes, there are several.
It's early.
You know, I kind of know
I know what I'm going to write.
One.
If you hadn't done that.
I wonder if you thought about it.
Please.
Watching cartoons, that stick.
Setting up the phone.
Being addicted.
That kind of thing,
Some kind of gadgetry.
I think.
I'm sure,
I might do that when I get a new phone, but I'm not into it.
I'm not addicted to it.
I'm not into it.
So you don't think it's the right answer?
It might be.
Maybe it already is.
I'm curious about the correct answer.
Please give me the correct answer.
What are you into now?
What I'm into now.
Well, what is it?
Let's see.
New.
music.
Do you listen to new music?
Yes, I do.
Oh, I'm lost. Music.
Music. It was cartoons.
Right now, there are playlists of new songs, newly released songs, you know.
I'm addicted to listening to them.
It doesn't matter what genre.
Yes, that's right.
I'll ask you to do it. Next.
Yes, please.
Please do.
Question 3.
Question 3. Where do you want to go most right now?
What did I say?
What? A country or something like that?
What do you think?
I think it was country.
I think it's a country.
But I think I've always wanted to go.
I don't know. I have two right now.
It's like, there's two in the wind.
I might want you to guess this one.
I'll go with the standard.
Okay, let's do it.
America.
LA.
Korea.
Ah, Korea.
But we're together here.
USA.United States.
I think that's probably what everyone's two choices are.
Yes, yes, yes. I think it's America or Korea.
That's right.
Then, let me ask you this.
Where do you want to go most right now?
The place I want to go most right now.
What? Where you want to go?
America.
Let's go together.
Let's go.
You got it right, Minamitsu-san.
That's great. Thank you very much.
That's nice.
You were just saying the other day that you wanted to go to America.
That's right.
I want to go to the Double Face series.
Oh, I was just saying.
For about three days.
Right. I knew it. Claire's trying to go in one day.
I can't do it anymore.
That's right. We'll just get on the plane and be done with it.
It's a runway.
It's a one-way trip.
It's hard.
That's why it's so far away. But I want to go.
But I think LA should be 0.5 for this.
Is it a little better?
Yes, 0.5.
I do want to go to LA,
I want to go to the US.
1?
0.5.
Ah, that's nice. It's finally here.
It's finally here.
Then, let's continue with the fourth question. Please.
Question 4.
Actually, I'm a ________.
Hmmm.
It's difficult for us.
I think this is very difficult.
If I had to decide whether it's a good thing or a bad thing, I'd say it's a bad thing.
Oh, I see.
OK.
Okay.
Now, please answer the question.
Let's see.
Actually, I tend to lose my personal belongings.
Actually, I scream easily.
I easily forget things.
Oh.
We're a bit alike.
Yes, we do.
I'm curious.
Then, please answer me.
Actually, I'm XX.
Actually me?
Actually, I am.
Recently there are many memories that exist that shouldn't exist.
There are many memories that exist lately that shouldn't be there.
I don't know.
But I'm sorry, sorry, sorry.
I'll put this in simpler terms, like forgetting something,
Lost and found, ah,
Ai?
Something close.
Oh, yeah.
What do you mean?
Is it something like that? Is it déjà vu?
That's why I'm having this thing,
I woke up yesterday,
It looked like my phone was here.
I went to where the phone was.
And it's not there.
And then, wait a minute, it's not there, it's not there, it's in a totally different place.
This happens a lot.
Are you okay?
I'm tired.
I'm tired. I've got a manuscript to write,Manuscripts, for example,
He says these things have been happening a lot lately.
Not at all.
You didn't scrape it off, did you?
I didn't scrape.
Not at all.
Well, I guess that's my judgment.
It's 0.5.
0.5?
But..,
Can I have it?
Oh, Tomochan.
Good, good, good.
And you?
0.5, 0.5.
That's good.
Let's continue.
Then we'll continue with the fifth question.
Question 5, please.
Question 5.
Please rearrange your morning routine.
Oh, I see.
Breakfast, makeup, getting dressed, brushing teeth, washing face, playing with sister. Second last time.
I see.
The second one is not the most recent.
Not at all.
It's surprisingly difficult.
I tried to write it while remembering the routine when I went to stay over.
Oh, wow.
Have you ever stayed over?
Yes, I have.
Now, let's see what you do.
Face wash breakfast, brush teeth, go to bed twice, play with my sister, change makeup and clothes.
Sleep 2 timesFace wash breakfastTooth brush teethChange clothesMakeupPlay
Go to bed twice, wash face, brush teeth, change clothes and make up.
I see. It's hard to say. It's pretty varied.
Then, please give me your answer. I wake up in the morning, go to bed twice, eat breakfast, wash my face, start doing my makeup, play with my sisters, change my clothes, and brush my teeth before leaving the house.
It was totally different. How much did I get right? In terms of order. Not nearly right.
Can I ask you one more time? I got two. Only the change of clothes was correct.
MisakiYou got two right. That's great. I didn't ask you how many were correct.
How many did you get right?
One...one...one...two points.
1.5, 0.5, 0.5, 3.5, 1.5, 1.5.
Oh, I have a feeling that I'm going to win.
Last. 6th question.
Are we on the same point? Yes, that's right. Whoever guesses the last one wins.
No, no, no, no, no. That's what happens. All that effort. Last person to guess wins.
Last person to guess wins. I was hoping you'd guess last.
Question 6. Please dance the chorus of the Girls Girls song.
So, I think it's okay for the winner. So you have to guess which song it is.
I don't need this much.
I danced to a song that didn't come out of nowhere.
This is a win-win situation, so it's okay. Don't worry. I'm going to start dancing now.
I'll start with that. Seino.
I'm Chiwa-pane.
What's going to happen now?
I wonder.
Please dance the chorus of the Girls Girls song.
Dance?
Umm, oh, ok.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What? Why?
Love?
What's that?
What is it?
You're dancing so well.
Maybe it's love.
Why do I have to say it too?
I've heard the word "chiwa-pane" once.
I knew it.
It was so hard.
It was so hard!
But you're winning.
We're winning. One time.
That's right.
By a good margin.
Then maybe...
Yes, let's go, together.
Yay!
We've got 4 cows!We are now at 4 cows!
Yes, that's right.
Thank you for watching!
If you liked this video
If you like this video, please give us a high rating, comment and
and subscribe to our channel.
Thank you very much.
So, thank you very much!
Bye bye.